Narrator: 1
Man: We stayed at the Hollywood Roosevelt for two nights.
It’s a really nice place – a very elegant, very "LA" hotel.
The service, atmosphere, and room were excellent, and we really enjoyed our stay.
But we had a really strange experience.
On the first night, we woke up at 3:30 in the morning.
There was a strange noise outside our door,
like someone softly playing a trumpet.
To tell you the truth, we were a little bit frightened.
Why would someone play the trumpet in the middle of the night?
Then we thought that it was probably another guest in the hall,
and maybe they were listening to music on their cell phone or something,
and we went back to sleep.
But on the second night, the same exact thing happened.
So, we just thought, strange, maybe
it’s because it’s an old hotel and the walls are thin.
But when we got home, we told the story to a friend,
and he told us that the Hollywood Roosevelt is haunted.
We looked on the internet, and we read that people say that room 928 has a ghost!
And our room was 926, the next room!
We sent an email to the Hollywood Roosevelt and told them about it,
and they sent us some really interesting information about the ghost stories.
We’d really like to stay in this fantastic hotel again, but maybe not in room 926!
Narrator: 2
Woman: I stayed at the Hollywood Roosevelt in May of last year with my husband.
It’s a beautiful hotel, with a great location.
It’s right on Hollywood Boulevard.
We were in a room on the eighth floor.
We knew that people said there were ghosts,
and we knew about room 928, but we weren’t worried at all.
We had a nice meal at a nearby restaurant and then we went to bed.
But in the middle of the night
– about three in the morning – we suddenly woke up and
we could hear loud noises from the room above us.
They were really loud noises – like people were dropping
their heavy suitcases on the floor.
Anyway, after two or three minutes, the noises stopped and we went back to sleep.
There weren’t any more strange noises, and we slept for the rest of the night.
The next morning, we went to reception and said,
“We slept very poorly last night – the people in the room
above us made so much noise.”
The man at reception asked for our room number and said, “Let me check.”
He looked on the computer and he said,
“The room above you is empty.”
So I said, “Are you sure?”
And he said, “Yes. The room above yours is room 928.
There wasn’t anybody in that room last night.”
We checked out of the hotel the same morning.
Never again!